但是功能不会因为该体验而改变，
But the function is not altered as result of that experience,
它不记得了。&gt；&gt；演讲者1：所以目标是保护
it doesn't remember that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So the goal is to protect
数组。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我们已经开始这样做了，
array. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Which we have started to do,
现在我们已经有了这个东西，在一个函数范围内，我们已经有了关闭它的方法。
now we've got the thing, in a function scope, we've got methods of close over it.
我们已经做得很好了，但是语言中有一个漏洞，
We've done all of that stuff well, but there is a vulnerability in the language,
这会阻碍我们的工作。&GT；&GT；演讲者1：我的意图是，
which will frustrate our work. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: My intention is just,
你只有一个返回对象，对吗？
and you just have the return object, right?
所以你可以创建一个新的，你是否可以潜在地定义一个新的，关键字
So you could make a new, could you potentially define a new, key of
只返回数组的函数。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：那么，你只是。
the function that just return array. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So, you just.
你会怎么做？&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的，
How would you do that? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah,
卡斯特。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：那么，
Castor. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So,
更明确一点。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：那么，
be more explicit. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So,
您可以调用存储的vector，或者传入包含数组的函数。
you call vector that store or you pass in a function that contains the array.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, but
您传入的函数是在外部创建的，对吗？
the function you pass in, is created on the outside, right?
所以当函数在外部时，函数不会在数组上关闭，所以，
So that function doesn't close over the array when it's on the outside, and so,
只有在内部创建的函数才是该闭包的一部分。
only functions created on the inside will be part of that closure.
&gt；&gt；[INAUDIBLE]。
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE].
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：有可能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It is possible to have
函数到系统对象的原型，这肯定是
functions to the prototypes of system objects, and that is definitely going
关心这个问题会解决的。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：如果你要，
to be concerned about that's going to fix. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: if you were to,
我想这就是约翰所说的，如果你要，
I think this is what John was saying, if you were to,
你仍然可以实现一个向量，然后你说，向量。
you can still achieve a vector, and then you say, vector.
获取数组等于函数返回，数组。
Get array equals function return, array.
但是数组是未定义的，因为它的影响范围是
But array is undefined, because its impact scope of
你创造它的地方。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：没错。
where you're creating it. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's right.
所以这很好，这是语言工作的地方
So that's good, that's a place where the language is working for
我们。&gt；&gt；[CROSSTALK]
us. &gt;&gt; [CROSSTALK]
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah,
这不是语言薄弱的地方。
that's not where the language is weak.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：如果从Vector继承，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: If you inherit from vector,
您是否可以访问[INAUDIBLE]。&gt；&gt；演讲者2：非常好的问题，
do you have access to the [INAUDIBLE]. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Really good question,
不，因为函数停止工作，比如JavaScopes，
no, because functions go stop work like JavaScopes,
你知道没有包装之类的东西。
you know there's no package kind of thing.
所以，不，你不能继承函数作用域的内容。
So, no you don't inherit the contents of a function scope.
你能摆弄一下那个函数吗。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：那么，向量，您的实例
Can you twiddle with that function. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So, vector, your instance
那个.get，里面有这个功能。
that.get, has this function in it.
你能不能，这是一个函数。
Can you, it is a function.
有没有什么方法可以操作这个函数的内脏一次
Is there some way to manipulate the guts of that function once
您有指向它的指针吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：没有。
you have a pointer to it? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
不，功能。
No, functions.
是的，你可以存储一个函数。
Yeah, you could store a function.
您可以使用STORE将函数放入数组中，然后
You could use store to put a function through an array and
然后使用get将其恢复。
then use get, to get it back out.
但是功能不会因为该体验而改变，
But the function is not altered as result of that experience,
它不记得了。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：函数没有
it doesn't remember that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The function doesn't have
您可以使用的任何属性
any properties that you could go and
挑。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
pick at. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：哪里更改，所以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Where change, so
当你下次打电话时，它会完全给你一些东西
that when you call the next time, it gives you something completely
不一样。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
different. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：如果我将函数附加到
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: If I tack a function onto
然后叫这个。
that and call this.
这台设备是否可以访问阵列？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：您可以
Does this have access to the array? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You are on to
一些东西。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：SO
something. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So
如果我调用了append on function code，把它搞砸了，
if I had called append on function code, screw it up,
如果把它搞砸了，并且说，这个.array等于一个新的数组。
and if screw it up, and said, this .array equals a new array.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不会是这个.array，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It wouldn't be this .array,
因为没有代表作用域内容的对象。
because there is not an object which represents The contents of the scope.
但这绝对是袭击的一部分。
But this is, definitely part of the attack.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我们可以改变Push，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Can we change push,
所以我们说的是阵列？
so that we said array?
我们改变了数组的原型推送，
We changed what the prototypical push of an array,
这样做，它将返回自己的值。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是，是
does so that, it returns its own value. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah
你越来越接近了。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。
you are getting close. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
好的，所以return(I)，第三个函数不返回任何东西。
Okay so the return (i), that, the third function doesn't return anything.
所以这不会把它弄出来的。
So that's not gonna get it out.
第二个不返回任何内容。
The second one doesn't return anything.
所以这不会把它弄出来的。
So that's not gonna get it out.
或者，实际上，如果你传入一个数组，
Or, actually, if you pass in an array,
为了储存，
to store,
你可以改变，或者
you could change, or
不可以，您可以传入一个数组进行追加，并更改push，以便push所做的事情。
no, you could pass in an array to append, and change push, so that what push does.
它接受你已经通过的东西，并推到它的末端，它本身。
It takes the thing that you've passed in, and pushes onto the end of it, itself.
所以你用这个数组调用append，然后得到数组的最后一件事，
So you call append with this array, and then you get the last thing of the array,
这就是你想要的数组。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不，那不起作用，
and that's the array you want. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, that wouldn't work,
是的，你在漂流，你差点就成功了。
yeah, you're drifting away, you almost had it.
你非常接近
You were very, very close
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：末尾推送函数
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Push a function at the end
使用append，然后使用get，
of the array, using append, and then you use get,
调用那个函数，所以。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你可以这样做。
to call that function, so. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You can do that.
但是，这个函数不记得那个，那个发生了。
But, the function, the function does not remember that, that happened.
所以它不会因此而改变。&GT；&GT；扬声器3：你好，
So it is not altered by that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: How do you,
在JavaScope中更改原型的功能，
in JavaScope change the function of a prototype,
你像雷达原型一样耍花招。推，现在，
you trick like a radar prototype .push, and now,
你会没事的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：就是这样。
you're gonna okay. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's exactly it.
是的，你可以去array.prototype.push。
Yeah, you could go to array.prototype.push.
但我们假设这一点已经解决了。
But we're assuming that, that's been fixed.
所以JavaScript设计的一个方面，
So one of the aspects of the design of JavaScript,
就是所有的东西都是解锁的，它的内脏暴露出来了，而且
is that everything is unlocked with its guts exposed, and
如果你想到安全，那显然是一件可怕的事情。
If you think about security, that's obviously a terrible thing.
所以我们假设，这个问题已经解决了。
So we're assuming that, that's been fixed.
所以我们关心的不仅仅是普通的性能
So we're concerned not just with the performance of ordinary
程序。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：SO
programs. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So
如果要存储函数，
if you were to store a function,
这称为.array&gt；&gt；扬声器4：you
that calls this .array &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: You
仍然无法访问数组。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：此.array
still wouldn't have access to array. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: This .array
不会带你去那里，但这本身会带你去那里。
won't get you there, but this itself will get you there.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：有很多次是这样的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: There were times this.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我知道了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I got it.
就是，我所描述的确实做到了，每个人都在雷达原型上。推。
It was, what I described exactly did it, everyone at the radar prototype.push.
等于函数a，括号零等于这个。
Equals functional a, a brackets zero equals this.
所以他们不是在创建数组一，二，
So they're not creating array one, two,
三四。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：对吗？
three, four. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：他们正在创建数组x，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: They are creating array x,
到数组中，然后我调用我的第一个arra.push传递x。
into array, and then I call My first array.push passing in x.
两位的空数组，取走了自己，使x的第一个元素。
The two bit empty array, took away itself made that the first element of x.
因此，它们进入其中，现在x，x的第一个元素，
So, they pass into it and now x, the first element of x,
就是我想黑掉的阵列。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
is the array I want to hack out. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right.
我已经说过几次了，我们不是在寻找阵列点原型，那就是
I've said it a couple of times, we're not looking for array dot prototype, that
我们假设，这个问题已经解决了。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我是
we're assuming that, that's been fixed. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I'm
对不起，数组点原型是固定在新的
sorry, Array dot prototype is fixed in the new
语言的版本。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不，我们假设在
version of language. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, we're assuming in
这个问题的背景，那个已经解决了，因为这件事，
the context of this problem, that, that's been fixed, because of the very thing,
你刚刚描述的。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：它与此无关
that you just described. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: It has nothing to do
使用Call方法？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：it
with using the call method? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It
不需要使用Call方法。
does not require use of the call method.